{
    "subject": "resource/Peter_Raw",
    "predicate": "property/deathPlace",
    "object": "Melbourne, Victoria",
    "human_readable": "Peter Raw died in Melbourne, Victoria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8049843311309814,
            "question": "Where did Peter Raw die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7066341638565063,
            "question": "What year did Peter Raw die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569856584072113,
            "question": "Are there any notable events associated with Peter Raw's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35256776213645935,
            "question": "Was Peter Raw known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34234505891799927,
            "question": "Where else might we find information about Peter Raw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3418179154396057,
            "question": "Were there any memorials held for Peter Raw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34009063243865967,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Peter Raw?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27979251742362976,
            "question": "What was Peter Raw's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22668005526065826,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Peter Raw's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2024635672569275,
            "question": "What is the state of Melbourne, Victoria?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Peter Raw died in Melbourne, Victoria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6853_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Peter Raw's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6853_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Peter Raw's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6853_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Peter Raw?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6853_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6853_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that \"On 15 July 1988 Raw died of lymphoma at Richmond in Melbourne.\" which supports the statement that Peter Raw died in Melbourne, Victoria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Peter Raw died at Richmond in Melbourne, which is a suburb of Melbourne, Victoria. Hence, he didn't die in Melbourne, Victoria but rather in one of its suburbs.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states he died at Richmond in Melbourne.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It is contradicted by the statement \"On 15 July 1988 Raw died of lymphoma at Richmond in Melbourne.\"",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context states that Peter Raw died on 15 July 1988 at Richmond, which is located in Melbourne, Victoria. However, it specifically mentions he was cremated after dying there, not in Melbourne itself.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}